Hi, I'm Jonathan Reibach. My presentation
was on DIDWebs and the connection between
KERI and the decentralized identifier
ecosystem. Well, I think KERI offers some
unique qualities that really help DIDWebs
be the strongest version of the DIDWeb
family of identifiers. Specifically, it
allows for the controller to explicitly
authorize information like host
information, path information. And it also
allows for much more convenience when
dealing with very, very long-lived
identifiers like over the span of decades,
a lifetime. I think those two advantages
are really strong for DIDWebs. I think if
the work that we're doing on DIDWebs
disappeared tomorrow, it would be too bad.
I think that there as long as there's a
decentralized identified identifier market
and infrastructure out there, having a
bridge between that ecosystem and the KERI
ecosystem makes a lot of sense. There are
going to be consumers of KERI information
that want to get that via a DID document
because their infrastructure is set up
that way. And I think if we lost DIDWebs,
KERI would lose a foothold in the
interoperability space. That would be too
bad.!